(Sheldon:)And I ask you, is it worth it?
(Howard:)Told you not to ask.
(Penny:)Well, Sheldon, you're his friend.
Friends give each other presents.
(Sheldon:)I accept your premise,
I reject your conclusion.
(Howard:)Try telling him
it's a non-optional social convention.
- What?
- Just do it.
[PENNY GROANS]
(Howard:)It's a non-optional social convention.
Ah, fair enough.
(Howard:)He came with a manual.
(Sheldon:)Question, how am I going to get Leonard
a present before the party?
I don't drive and the things available
in walking distance...
(Sheldon:)...are a Thai restaurant
and a gas station.
(Sheldon:)I could wrap up an order of mee krob
and a couple of lottery scratchers.
(Penny:)Okay, let's do this.
I will drive Sheldon to get a present.
- Howard, get rid of Leonard for two hours.
- No problem.
(Penny:)And then, Raj, you bring the stuff
across the hall and start setting up.
- What if guests show up?
- Entertain them.